http://www.academyolmo.com/en/privacy/

Skip to main navigation
Skip to content
Navigation path
You are here:
Home > Privacy Policy
Do you want to remove all the cookies set by this site?If you have logged in, you will have to do it again.Remove cookies
The Web Site (after also «Service») URL http://www.academyolmo.com groups some personal data.
The processing of personal data owner (after also «Owner»)
Centro Culturale Academy Olmo
Registered Address: P.tta Santa Maria in Girone, 1, 47010 Portico e S.Benedetto (FC)
VAT Number: 04068590407
Telephone: +39 0543967053
Email: info@academyolmo.com
Three essential rules on the processing of personal data
Privacy – We respect your privacy. Without your authorization we will not share your personal data (e. g. name, surname, email, telephone number, date of birth and sex) with external people, which are not included in the management of this Service, unless required by law.
Management – On the other hand, these and other information may be used by external technical services and communications, just to improve your experience of using the Service. You can at any time request to the Holder the list of these suppliers.
Periods – At any time you can know your data being processed, to verify or request the modification, deletion or discontinuation of treatment.
Processing of personal data procedure
The processing of the data needed to make use of this service is carried out in two distinct modes.
1. Data processed directly by the Service
The Service needs your direct authorization to let you use the following modules (all or a subset).
Registration and User Login
Purpose
Data
Procedure
Cookie
Place
Notes
authentication, content personalization, statistics
(all or a subset) name, surname, company, VAT number, fiscal code, password, email, telephone number, date of birth, sex, billing address, shipping address
filling in the respective form or through social login
session cookie necessary for identification (technical cookie)
on request cookie necessary for identification of future sessions (technical cookie)
Service hosting
backup among the Owner
password encryption algorithm hash blowfish
Comments System
Purpose
Data
Procedure
Cookie
Place
Notes
identifying the author of a comment
name, email, IP address
filling in the relevant module
on request using cookies to prefill the form in the future comments (technical cookie)
Service hosting
backup among the Owner
--
Contact Form
Purpose
Data
Procedure
Cookie
Place
Notes
sending a user's message to the owner
(all or a subset) name, surname, company, email, telephone number, address
compiling of the respective module
--
Service hosting
backup among the Owner
email to the Owner
--
Booking Form
Purpose
Data
Procedure
Cookie
Place
Notes
booking request (e.g. request for a hotel room, order of a product, answer to a notice...)
(all or a subset) name, surname, company, VAT number, fiscal code, password, email, telephone number, date of birth, sex, billing address, shipping address
filling in the relevant module
--
Service hosting
backup among the Owner
email to the Owner
for any digital payment you make use of third party service (e.g. PayPal)
2. Data processed indirectly by third party service providers whose service uses
The Service, with the purpose of improving your viewing experience, can integrate external suppliers of services, regulated by the respective privacy policies.
Google Analytics
Service Provider
Purpose
Data
Procedure
Cookie
Place
Notes
Google Inc.
statistics on access to the Service
complete or partial IP address, user agent, employment's data of the Service
automatically during the use of the Service
cookie employment in support of the analysis (cookie profiling)
Google Inc. server in the USA
Google Analytics homepage: https://www.google.com/analytics/
Google Privacy Policy: https://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html
Google Analytics Privacy Policy: https://www.google.com/intl/it/policies/privacy/
Mailchimp
Service Provider
Purpose
Data
Procedure
Cookie
Place
Notes
Mailchimp Inc.
newsletter
(all or a subset) name, surname, company, email, telephone number, address
filling in the respective form on the web site
authorization through other modalities (contact the Owner for more information)
--
Mailchimp Inc. server in the USA
Mailchimp home page: http://mailchimp.com/
Mailchimp Privacy Policy: http://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/
Facebook Social Plugin
Service Provider
Purpose
Data
Procedure
Cookie
Place
Notes
Facebook Inc.
social marketing
no information sharing by the Service, where the Plugin is incorporated
user's interactions with the Plugin
cookies employment to support the analysis and the content personalization (cookie profiling)
Facebook Inc. server in the USA
Facebook's social plugin homepage: https://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins
Facebook Policy Privacy: https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation
Twitter Social Plugin
Service Provider
Purpose
Data
Procedure
Cookie
Place
Notes
Twitter Inc.
social marketing
no information sharing by the Service, where the Plugin is incorporated
user's interactions with the Plugin
cookies employment to support the analysis and the content personalization (cookie profiling)
Twitter Inc. server in the USA
Twitter's social plugin homepage: https://get.fabric.io/native-social
Twitter Privacy Policy: https://twitter.com/privacy?lang=it
YouTube Video
Service Provider
Purpose
Data
Procedure
Cookie
Place
Notes
Google Inc.
integration of video inside the Service
no information sharing by the Service, where the video is incorporated
user's interactions with the video
cookies employment to support the analysis and the content personalization (cookie profiling)
Google Inc. server in the USA
YouTube home page: http://www.youtube.com/
Google Privacy Policy: https://www.google.it/intl/it/policies/privacy/
Violations
The data being processed can be used for the defense of the owner in the case of abuse of the Service or of an external service by you or third parties.
Privacy Policy Upgrade
The Owner reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, informing you about it in this same page, while maintaining the same level of protection for your information.
Legal References
This Privacy Policy in written in accordance with the law 13 of the Decree 196/03 “Code concerning the protection of personal data”. The user can at any time demand the right expressed in the art. 7 of the Decree. and assert one's own rights by referring directly to the Owner.
For further information, read the article 13 and read the article 7.
Disable cookies
The user can delete the cookies directly through his browser. Here are the links to the management procedures of the most popular browsers cookie:
Microsoft Windows Explorer
Google Chrome
Mozilla Firefox
Apple Safari
To know the cookie profiling saved to your device and to disable them individually, please refer to the following link: youronlinechoices.com
Glossary
Cookie:
small file that a website stores on your computer to store useful information (and sometimes necessary) to the proper functioning of the site. (For further information: wikipedia)
Technical Cookie:
they are cookies that are used to keep the session active or to perform a requested action by the user within the Service.
Cookie profiling:
they are cookie that are used (generally from third parts) to mark the user's surfing on the web and to create profiles on his tastes, habits, choices etc.
Session:
time interval in which a single user may use the Service. (For further information: wikipedia)
Plugin:
small specific application, which can be integrated inside a Service. (For further information: wikipedia)
Server:
computer that provides services to other computers over the network. (For further information: wikipedia)
Hosting:
service that rents its servers and network connectivity to host a website and make it accessible through the web. (For further information: wikipedia)
Backup:
data security copy inside archives of mass storage. (For further information: wikipedia)
Newsletter Name:Surname:* La tua Email:* Do you consent to data processing?YesNo
Iscriviti
×
Privacy - Newsletter
Centro Culturale Academy Olmo will process the personal information you provide in this form in compliance with the GDPR and the Privacy Code.
By submitting this form you consent to the processing of personal data necessary for registration to our mailing list with the intention of receiving informative and/or commercial communications from us, in accordance with our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service.
By submitting this form you also consent to the processing of personal data in accordance with the Privacy Policy and Terms of Service of MailChimp, the software used for the automated management of this mailing list.
At any time you can withdraw your consent to the processing of personal data used in this mailing list, change the reception settings and/or unsubscribe through appropriate links that you will find in the emails you will receive. In addition, you can always exercise your rights regarding the processing of personal data by sending a request to info@academyolmo.com.
To consent to the processing of personal data you must first complete all the required fields.
Back
Take a few seconds to read.
I accept the conditions
I reject the conditions
This website uses technical cookies. Do you also want to consent to the use of third-party cookies for statistics and personalized content, as per our Privacy Policy? You can always change your mind later.
I consent
I decline
